

# Albertus Gagas Pradana Dian Nugraha

UI/UX Designer

#### PORTFOLIO

# bit.ly/Portfolio-Albertus

#### CONTACTS

- in /albertuspradana
- □ pradanaalbertus@gmail.com

# ABOUT ME

I'm Albert, a UI/UX designer who loves creating beautiful and meaningful products through design. As an information engineering graduate, I am well-versed in code and software development. For me, design is not just about aesthetics, but also the value it brings, the research and data behind it, and its practicality for development.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Synrgy ACADEMY Batch 3**

2021

UI/UX Design Scholarship Awardee.

## **Universitas Gadjah Mada**

2017 - 2021

Information Engineering (minor in Software Engineering).

## Mamicamp 2020

2020

Front-End Developer Class.

### SKILLS

## Design

Ideation, information architecture, wireframing, prototyping, icon design, multi-platform UI design

### Research

In-depth interview, competitive analysis, affinity mapping, usability testing

## WORKING EXPERIENCES

# synapsis.id - UI/UX Designer Freelance

Dec 2022 - Present

- Create user-centered interface designs for partners' needs
- Collaborate with stakeholders and engineering team to ensure successful project delivery

# imuni - UI/UX Designer

Jan 2022 - Present

 Designed integrated system (mobile app for clients and a web-based admin back office) from scratch, adopted as part of imuni's digital ecosystem.

## **BuildWith Angga - UI Designer Intern**

Sep - Dec 2021

- Responsible for designing BuildWith Angga internal projects
- Responsible for designing website builder template for GetShayna (previously Elements by BWA)

# Pazel Group - UI/UX Designer Freelance

Jan - Apr 2021

 Responsible for designing Pazel Cloud, an internal POS system to support Pazel Group business

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Foodie**

A catering website that aims to help WFH moms provide healthy food for their families